toplinesearch.com 2005-11-09

# Thelifesearch.com

**Privacy Policy**

Your online privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we provide a link to it on every page of our website.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices or the www.thelifesearch.com website .

Thelifesearch uses information for the following general purposes:

\- to contact you;  
\- to improve our site and services;  
\- research;  
\- anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Thelifesearch PPC SearchEngine provides links to many other websites that are beyond our control. Websites that we link to may have privacy and security policies that differ from Thelifesearch PPC SearchEngine. Please understand that we are not responsible, in any manner, for the privacy, security practices, or content of such websites.

Thelifesearch does not rent, sell, or share your personal information with any third party, non-affiliated companies, except under the following circumstances:  
\- we provide information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Thelifesearch under strict agreements. These companies may use your information to help Thelifesearch communicate with you about offers from Thelifesearch and our marketing partners;  
\- when requested by means of a court order or other legal process.

Thelifesearch does not provide any individually identifiable information to advertisers.

 **Cookies**

Thelifesearch may set and access Thelifesearch cookies on your computer. Thelifesearch allows advertisers to set and access their cookies on your computer.

**Advertising**

Thelifesearch may use our own advertising as well as third party advertising agencies on our website. Thelifesearch cannot be held responsible for anything contained within the sites of our partners, members, or advertisers.

**Permission To Use Your Content**

By transmitting any suggestions, information, identification, material, or other content ("content") to Thelifesearch, you automatically grant us the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, redistribute, transmit, perform and display such content (in whole or part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in such content. Further, we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, and suggestions contained in any communications you send to Thelifesearch for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to creating, manufacturing and marketing products and/or services using such information.

**General**

You can edit your Thelifesearch account information at any time. Communications from Thelifesearch, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters, are considered part of Thelifesearch your membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. We limit access to information about you to employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Thelifesearch account information is password-protected.

**Notification of Changes To The Privacy Policy:**

Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If at some point in the future, Thelifesearch PPC SearchEngine changes the usage practices that affect any of your personally identifiable information, We will notify you by email of the changes. At the time of that message you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by sending an email message to the follow address: webmaster@thelifesearch.com

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect by editing your account information directly using the appropriate control panel on our website. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or corrections to any of your personally identifiable information.

**How To Contact Us:**

If you have any questions about the Thelifesearch PPC SearchEngine privacy commitment, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us please contact: **webmaster@thelifesearch.com**
